NASA正在建造人类唯一一款能安全运送昂贵货物、宇航员
NASA is building the only rocket capable of safely sending our most precious cargo, astronauts,
飞往月球甚至更远的深空任务的火箭
on bold exploration missions to the Moon and beyond.
这一切正在发生！
This is happening now!
在我们建造太空发射系统SLS的时候
As we build the Space Launch System, or SLS,
每个零件都要仔细检查并测试以保证其正常工作
every piece has to be scrutinized and tested to make sure it works properly,
因为SLS将把人类送到从未到过的太空深处
because the Space Launch System will send humans farther beyond Earth than they have ever traveled.
工程师必须保证每个零件在太空的极端条件下仍可以正常使用
Engineers must ensure every single part can operate in the extreme environment of space
并同时保证安全，因为上面还有人呢
and be as safe as possible because astronauts are on board.
NASA管这叫“载人评估”一枚火箭
NASA calls this “human rating” a space vehicle.  Let’s take a closer look.
载人评估是一项严密的过程，会把相当多的因素考虑进去
Human rating is a thorough process that consists of many variables being taken into account
包括从设计、建造、发射载人火箭到飞船与成员返回地球
to safely design, build and launch a crewed spacecraft and return that spacecraft, and its crew safely to the earth.
其中一个关键零件就是(212英尺)64.6米的芯级
A key component is the rocket’s 212-foot-tall core stage.
它是这枚世界上最大的火箭中最大的零件
The core stage is the largest piece of the world’s most powerful rocket.
但在它和火箭其他部分总装到一起之前
But before it’s assembled with the other parts of the rocket,
芯级的五段都要安装上千个传感器、线缆、燃料管线、紧固件等等
the Core Stage’s 5 sections are outfitted with thousands of sensors, cabling, fuel lines, fasteners and many, many more parts.
SLS的发动机段内装有四台RS-25发动机
The Space Launch System Engine Section is home to four RS-25 engines
还有数英里的线缆、航电设备、推力结构、燃料管线和传感器
and miles of cables, avionics, thrust structures, fuel lines, and sensors.
工程师会对发动机段的主体结构进行压力测试
Engineers stress-tested the Engine Section’s main structure subjecting it to massive forces
保证其满足载人深空飞行的强度需求
to prove it met the strict requirements for flying humans to deep space.
芯级有两个燃料来源：
The Core Stage contains two separate fuel sources:
液氢箱和液氧箱，它们共同在飞行中给火箭发动机供给燃料
The Liquid Hydrogen Tank, and the Liquid Oxygen Tank which fuel the rocket engines for flight.
当它们在飞行之前总装的时候
While the flight ready tanks are being outfitted,
两个测试部件会准备验证它们能经受起飞与上升过程中的巨大压力
twin test articles are being prepared to prove their strength against the incredible forces
encountered during lift-off and flight.
而两个燃料罐的连接部分Intertank则要承受最极端的压力
The rigid Intertank that connects these two fuel tanks experiences the most extreme forces.
所以它和芯级其他地方不同，没有使用焊接
So, it is not welded together like the rest of the core stage
而是使用专为不断增加的压力而制造的超过14000个螺栓与紧固件
but is built for increased strength with more than 14,000 bolts and fasteners holding it together.
它本身也要进行测试
It too must be tested.
航电设备、相机与火箭的三台飞行计算机则被安装于芯级顶端部分
The avionics, cameras and the rocket’s three flight computers are being housed in the Forward Skirt section of the Core Stage.
每个设备都要经过震动、极端温度等全面的测试
Each piece is shaken, exposed to extreme temperatures and thoroughly tested
以保证其可经受严酷的飞行条件
to guarantee it can withstand the rigors of flight.
我们现在还在组装火箭的主要零件
Today we are outfitting major parts of the world’s only rocket
这款火箭是世界唯一被设计、制造用于送人类飞往月球与更远地方的
designed and build to fly humans to the moon and beyond.
不久之后，我们将把它组装好
Soon, we put it all together.
但那是之后的事情了，那么再见啦
But that is the next step. See you then.